Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files H
    - Hale, Clara (Box A-51, Folder 44)
      Also one folded newspaper clipping from the Tampa Tribune-Times about African-American Alcee Hastings announcing his candidacy for U.S. Senate.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Peterkin Photo, Coreen Simpson, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Moore, Angela Harris
    - Hale, Clara (Box A-51, Folder 45)
      Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Monmouth College, Pictorial Enterprise
    - Hale, Frank W. (Dr.) (Box A-51, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Ohio State University
    - Hale, Lorraine (Box A-51, Folder 47)
    - Hale, Phale D. (Dr.) (Box A-51, Folder 48)
    - Hale, William (Box A-51, Folder 49)
      Photographer if identified: Henry O. Crawford
    - Haley, Alex (Box A-51, Folder 50)
    - Haley, Candy (Box A-51, Folder 51)
    - Haley, Julius (Box A-51, Folder 52)
    - Haley, William (Box A-51, Folder 53)
    - Hall, Albert (Box A-51, Folder 54)
    - Hall, Alexander (Bishop) (Box A-51, Folder 55)
    - Hall, Aaron (Box A-51, Folder 56)
    - Hall, Arsenio (Box A-51, Folder 57)
      Also one velox print. Velox is loose and stuck to the image side of the print.
    - Hall, Bernice E. (Box A-51, Folder 58)
    - Hall, Carl (Box A-51, Folder 59)
    - Hall, Charles H. (Box A-51, Folder 60)
      Photographer if identified: Sgt. Maj. Abrains/PIO/Ft. Dix NJ
    - Hall, Charles L. (Box A-51, Folder 61)
    - Hall, Charles W. (Rev.) (Box A-51, Folder 62)
    - Hall, Charles W. (Rev.) (Box A-51, Folder 63)
    - Hall, Chris A. (Box A-51, Folder 64)
      One velox print mounted on heavy board with cut-out animated character pasted on recto.
    - Hall, Clarissa (Box A-51, Folder 65)
    - Hall, Claude (Box A-51, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Serating
    - Hall, David (Box A-51, Folder 67)
    - Hall, Delores (Box A-51, Folder 68)
      One folder inside folder.
      Photographer if identified: Martha Swope, The Lighthouse/Public Relations Dept.
    - Hall, Earl (Box A-51, Folder 69)
    - Hall, Edmond (Box A-51, Folder 70)
    - Hall, Edward (Box A-51, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Alfred Puhn
    - Hall, Edwin (Box A-51, Folder 72)
    - Hall, Ernest (Rev.) (Box A-51, Folder 73)
    - Hall, Frances (Box A-51, Folder 74)
      Newspaper clipping with image adhered to verso.
    - Hall, Fred J. (Box A-51, Folder 75)
    - Hall, Harold A. (Box A-51, Folder 76)
    - Hall, Henry L. (Box A-51, Folder 77)
    - Hall, Horace (Box A-51, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Parkway Studios, Harris Photo
    - Hall, Howard (Box A-51, Folder 79)
    - Hall, Ingrid (Box A-51, Folder 80)
    - Hall, James (Box A-51, Folder 81)
    - Hall, James (Box A-51, Folder 82)
    - Hall, James R., Jr. (Major General) (Box A-51, Folder 83)
    - Hall, James C. (Dr.) (Box A-51, Folder 84)
    - Hall, James E. (Box A-51, Folder 85)
    - Hall, James Alexander and Marcia Blair (Box A-51, Folder 86)
      Photographer if identified: Negro Press Photo Service Inc.
    - Hall, Jim (Box A-51, Folder 87)
    - Hall, Jimmy (Box A-51, Folder 88)
    - Hall, John (Box A-51, Folder 89)
    - Hall, Joseph (Box A-51, Folder 90)
    - Hall, Juanita (Box A-51, Folder 91)
    - Hall, Julia (Box A-51, Folder 92)
    - Hall, K.R. (Box A-51, Folder 93)
    - Hall, Katherine (Box A-51, Folder 94)
      Photographer if identified: Sinclair Studio
    - Hall, Ken (Box A-51, Folder 95)
    - Hall, Kermit (Box A-51, Folder 96)
    - Hall, Linder (Box A-51, Folder 97)
      Print is badly darkened and giving off a strong chemical odor.
    - Hall, Marguerite (Box A-51, Folder 98)
    - Hall, Marie Rose, also Mary Hall (Box A-51, Folder 99)
    - Hall, Martin B. (Box A-51, Folder 100)
    - Hall, Nell (Box A-51, Folder 101)
      Loose typescript caption has separated from the verso of one of the prints.
      Photographer if identified: Editta Sherman
    - Hall of Fame (Box A-51, Folder 102)
    - Hall & Oates (Box A-51, Folder 103)
    - Hall, Randy (Box A-51, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: Gary Gershoff
    - Hall, Renee (Box A-51, Folder 105)
    - Hall, Robert O., Jr. (Box A-51, Folder 106)
    - Hall, Samantha (Box A-51, Folder 107)
    - Hall, Sandra (Box A-51, Folder 108)
    - Hall, Stanley (Box A-51, Folder 109)
    - Hall, Truvillus II (Box A-51, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Army/William P. Garbutt/Comm Div Photo Facilities/Fort Gordon GA
    - Hall, Tyrone (Box A-51, Folder 111)
    - Hall, Vondie (Box A-51, Folder 112)
    - Hall, W.J. (Rev.) (Box A-51, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: Monclova, Rufus Merritt
    - Hall, Wanda (Box A-51, Folder 114)
    - Hall, William (Box A-51, Folder 115)
    - Hall, William (Box A-51, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: Chuck Smith
    - Hall, William, Jr. (Box A-51, Folder 117)
    - Hall, William M. (Dr.) (Box A-51, Folder 118)
    - Hall, Willie (Box A-51, Folder 119)
      Contains one folder labeled "Hall, Willie (See Tony Jackson)."
    - Hall, Yvette (Box A-51, Folder 120)
    - Hall, Edward (Mr. and Mrs.) (Box A-51, Folder 121)
    - Hallelujah, Baby (Box A-51, Folder 122)
    - Halleron, Mary (Box A-51, Folder 123)
      Photographer if identified: Arthur Corr
    - Hallett, Denise (Box A-51, Folder 124)
    - Halley, Ann (Box A-51, Folder 125)
    - Halley, Ronnie (Owner of Ronnie's Haberdashery) (Box A-51, Folder 126)
    - Halliburton, Barbara (Mrs.) (Box A-51, Folder 127)
      Polaroid print adhered to center of one typescript leaf.
    - Halliburton, Norman (Box A-51, Folder 128)
    - Halliday, Frederick (Box A-51, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Standard Photo Service Inc.
    - Halloman, John L. S., Jr. (Dr.) (Box A-51, Folder 130)
      Photographer if identified: Scott Henderson
    - Halloween Party (Box A-51, Folder 131)
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley Photo Services, Muller Studio, Rufus Merritt
    - Hallums, Charles (Box A-51, Folder 132)
    - Ha-lo the Great (Box A-52, Folder 1)
    - Halper, Rue (Box A-52, Folder 2)
      Photographer if identified: SCLC Photo
    - Halpern, Sandra (Box A-52, Folder 3)
    - Halsell, Grace (Box A-52, Folder 4)
    - Halston, James Jr. (Box A-52, Folder 5)
    - Haltaufderhyde, Patricia (Box A-52, Folder 6)
    - Halyard, Howard E. (Box A-52, Folder 7)
    - Halyard, Lee (Box A-52, Folder 8)
    - Hamasho, Mustafa (Box A-52, Folder 9)
    - Hambrick, Priscilla (Box A-52, Folder 10)
    - Hambuc, James (Box A-52, Folder 11)
    - Hameen, Jessie III (Box A-52, Folder 12)
    - Hamer, Daisy (Box A-52, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Photography, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise
    - Hamer, Fannie Lou (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Ed Bagwell (News Voice International)
    - Hamer, G. Joyce (Box A-52, Folder 15)
    - Hamill, Pete (Box A-52, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Drake Studios
    - Hamilton, Ada (Box A-52, Folder 17)
      Photographer if identified: McLean Photo
    - Hamilton, Alexander (Box A-52, Folder 18)
    - Hamilton, Anne (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 19)
    - Hamilton, Bermuda (Box A-52, Folder 20)
      Photographer if identified: Bermuda News Bureau
    - Hamilton, Bernie (Box A-52, Folder 21)
    - Hamilton, Charles T. (Box A-52, Folder 22)
      Also three velox prints.
    - Hamilton, Charles V. (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 23)
      One print has press release attached with paperclip. Also one velox print.
    - Hamilton, Chico (Box A-52, Folder 24)
    - Hamilton, Effie (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 25)
      Photographer if identified: Camera Arts Studio
    - Hamilton, Frederick (Box A-52, Folder 26)
    - Hamilton, Gail (Box A-52, Folder 27)
    - Hamilton, George (Box A-52, Folder 28)
      Photographer if identified: Ken Regan (Mexican National Tourist Council)
    - Hamilton, Gerald (Box A-52, Folder 29)
    - Hamilton, Harold (Atty.) (Box A-52, Folder 30)
    - Hamilton, Harold A. (Box A-52, Folder 31)
    - Hamilton, Holly (Box A-52, Folder 32)
      One print has photocopied newspaper clipping attached with paperclip. Also one velox print.
    - Hamilton, Irving (Mr. + Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 33)
    - Hamilton, Jean (Box A-52, Folder 34)
      Note on folder: "(See Charles Knight)."
    - Hamilton, Jesse (Box A-52, Folder 35)
      Photographer if identified: Ted Burrows
    - Hamilton, Jimmie (Box A-52, Folder 36)
    - Hamilton, John (Box A-52, Folder 37)
    - Hamilton, John Jr. (Box A-52, Folder 38)
      Photographer if identified: Cy Morris
    - Hamilton, Ken (Box A-52, Folder 39)
    - Hamilton, Kim (Box A-52, Folder 40)
    - Hamilton, Leo W. (Box A-52, Folder 41)
      Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, Bill Hayes Photography
    - Hamilton, Lester Y. (Box A-52, Folder 42)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Customs Photo Port of New York
    - Hamilton, Lynn (Box A-52, Folder 43)
    - Hamilton, Madrid T. (Box A-52, Folder 44)
    - Hamilton, Marmetta (Box A-52, Folder 45)
    - Hamilton, Marrietta (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 46)
    - Hamilton, Melba Butler (Box A-52, Folder 47)
      Folder label reads "Melba Butler-Hamilton."
    - Hamilton, Olivia (Box A-52, Folder 48)
    - Hamilton, Phil (Box A-52, Folder 49)
    - Hamilton, Rhonda (Box A-52, Folder 50)
    - Hamilton, Roy (Box A-52, Folder 51)
      Also includes funeral program and one typescript leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bill Carter, Austin, James Gilbert
    - Hamilton, Roy (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 52)
    - Hamilton, Samuel C. (Box A-52, Folder 53)
    - Hamilton, Scott (Box A-52, Folder 54)
    - Hamilton, Stephen C. (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 55)
      One velox and one typescript leaf.
    - Hamilton, Thelma (Box A-52, Folder 56)
    - Hamilton, Virginia (Box A-52, Folder 57)
      Photographer if identified: Barbara Goldberg, Audree Distad
    - Hamilton, William L. (Box A-52, Folder 58)
      Photographer if identified: Louis C. Ward, Gene Luttenberg
    - Hamilton, Willie L. (Box A-52, Folder 59)
    - Hamler, Meredith (Box A-52, Folder 60)
    - Hamler, Sonya (Box A-52, Folder 61)
    - Hamlet, James F. (Brig. Gen.) (Box A-52, Folder 62)
    - Hamlet, Sarah Hyde (Box A-52, Folder 63)
      Name on back of print given as "Sarah Hyde-Hamlet."
    - Hamlet, Arlene H. (Box A-52, Folder 64)
    - Hamlin, Billy (Box A-52, Folder 65)
    - Hamlin, John (Box A-52, Folder 66)
    - Hamlin, Lew Eleanor (Box A-52, Folder 67)
    - Hamlin, Pamela (Box A-52, Folder 68)
    - Hamlin, Tim (Box A-52, Folder 69)
    - Hammer, Brenda (Box A-52, Folder 70)
    - Hammer, Jack (Box A-52, Folder 71)
      Photographer if identified: Billy Pierce Jr.
    - Hammer, Jolie (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 72)
    - Hammer, Joyce (Box A-52, Folder 73)
    - Hammerstein, Oscar (Box A-52, Folder 74)
      Note on folder: "(Deceased)."
      Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Syndicate
    - Hammerstein, Oscar II (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 75)
    - Hammock, Charles (Box A-52, Folder 76)
    - Hammock, Edward (Box A-52, Folder 77)
    - Hammond, Albert (Rev.) (Box A-52, Folder 78)
      Photographer if identified: Del Ankers, Studio Reneé
    - Hammond, Allen S. IV (Box A-52, Folder 79)
    - Hammond, Bertha Adele (Box A-52, Folder 80)
    - Hammond, Charles Jr. (Box A-52, Folder 81)
    - Hammond, John (Box A-52, Folder 82)
    - Hammond, Johnny (Box A-52, Folder 83)
    - Hammond, Lillian (Box A-52, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: Russ Carter Studio
    - Hammond, Lydia (Box A-52, Folder 85)
    - Hammond, Mark (Box A-52, Folder 86)
    - Hammond, Phyllis (Box A-52, Folder 87)
    - Hammond, Robert E. (Box A-52, Folder 88)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Coast Guard Photo
    - Hammond, Sam (Box A-52, Folder 89)
    - Hammond, Terry (Box A-52, Folder 90)
    - Hammonds, Earlene (Box A-52, Folder 91)
    - Hamner, Curley (Box A-52, Folder 92)
    - Hamphill, Julius (Box A-52, Folder 93)
    - Hampton, Albert E. (Box A-52, Folder 94)
    - Hampton, Carl (Box A-52, Folder 95)
    - Hampton, Clarence (Box A-52, Folder 96)
    - Hampton, David (Box A-52, Folder 97)
    - Hampton, Elwood (Box A-52, Folder 98)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Smith
    - Hampton, Fred (Box A-52, Folder 99)
    - Hampton, Fred (Box A-52, Folder 100)
      Note on folder: "(See Eldridge Cleaver)."
    - Hampton, Hope (Box A-52, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Eric Schweikardt
    - Hampton Institute (Box A-52, Folder 102)
      Two prints are illustrated graphs. Includes multiple issues of the "News from Hampton Institute" as well as press releases.
    - Hampton, James (Box A-52, Folder 103)
    - Hampton, Judith (Box A-52, Folder 104)
    - Hampton, Karl P. (Box A-52, Folder 105)
    - Hampton, Lawrence (Box A-52, Folder 106)
    - Hampton, Lionel (Box A-52, Folder 107)
      Note on folder: "1 of 4 folders." Also several typescript leaves and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, News Voice International, Bill Mark, Sally Mueller, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Cecil Layne, Kas Heppner (Metropolitan Photo Service), Martin Gross, David McAdams, Allen Morgan
      Number of Prints: 43
    - Hampton, Lionel (Box A-52, Folder 108)
      Note on folder: "2 of 4 folders." Also press release, one flier, one pamphlet, and three velox prints.
      Photographer if identified: Kas Heppner, Bert Smith, Harris Photo, News Events Photo Service, Virgin Islands Government Office of P.R., Big M Photo Service, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Billy Pierce Jr., George West, Ricco Richardson
      Number of Prints: 47
    - Hampton, Lionel (Box A-52, Folder 109)
      Note on folder: "3 of 4 folders." One print is an illustrated caricature. Also one press release and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bill Moore, Peterkin Photo, Monroe S. Frederick II, Peter Pouchon, Pictorial Enterprise, Wide World Photos, Shelley Brown
      Number of Prints: 64
    - Hampton, Lionel (Box A-52, Folder 110)
      Note on folder: "Damaged photos 4/4." All prints are stuck together with paste and/or damaged; print count is approximate.
    - Hampton, Paula (Box A-52, Folder 111)
    - Hampton, Slide (Box A-52, Folder 112)
    - Hampton, Verna (Box A-52, Folder 113)
    - Hamrick, Melzie (Box A-52, Folder 114)
    - Hams, Bethel J. (Box A-52, Folder 115)
    - Hanbrick, Priscilla (Box A-52, Folder 116)
    - Hanbury, Raymond (Box A-52, Folder 117)
      Press release stapled to recto.
    - Hanchard, George (Box A-52, Folder 118)
    - Hancock, Barbara (Box A-52, Folder 119)
    - Hancock, Eugene (Box A-52, Folder 120)
    - Hancock, Herbie (Box A-52, Folder 121)
      One press release and three velox prints.
    - Hancock, Jean E. (Box A-52, Folder 122)
    - Hancock, Mario (Bro.) (Box A-52, Folder 123)
    - Hand, Cookie (Box A-52, Folder 124)
      Note on folder: "Also in here is (Miss Margaret Hand)."
      Photographer if identified: Robert L. Haggins, Bramson Studio
    - Handball (Box A-52, Folder 125)
    - Handel, Morris (Box A-52, Folder 126)
      Photographer if identified: Banner Photographers
    - Handicapped (Box A-52, Folder 127)
      Photographer if identified: BPI photo
    - Handing, James H. (Box A-52, Folder 128)
    - Handlin, Bernard (Box A-52, Folder 129)
    - Handman, Edward (Box A-52, Folder 130)
    - Hands Across America (Box A-52, Folder 131)
      Folder label reads "Fighting Sickle Cell Children Help Children "Hands Across America" 1986."
    - Hands Club, The (Box A-52, Folder 132)
      Photographer if identified: Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Rufus Merritt
    - Handy, Antoinette (Box A-52, Folder 133)
    - Handy, Gloria (Box A-52, Folder 134)
    - Handy, John (Box A-52, Folder 135)
    - Handy, Louise (Box A-52, Folder 136)
      One print is Polaroid.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Bill Carter
    - Handy, W.C. Jr. (Box A-52, Folder 137)
    - Hanes, Gordon (Box A-52, Folder 138)
    - Haney, Madelyn (Box A-52, Folder 139)
      Photographer if identified: E. Greene
    - Hank, Henry (Box A-52, Folder 140)
    - Hankerson, Barry (Box A-52, Folder 141)
    - Hankins, Freeman P. (Sen.) (Box A-52, Folder 142)
      Photographer if identified: Woods
    - Hankins, George (Box A-52, Folder 143)
    - Hankins, M.J. (Mr.) (Box A-52, Folder 144)
    - Hankins, Milton J. (Box A-52, Folder 145)
    - Hankins, Nancy (Box A-52, Folder 146)
    - Hanley, Edward (Box A-52, Folder 147)
      Photographer if identified: Dalman James Jr.
    - Hanley, Kathy (Box A-52, Folder 148)
    - Hanley, Lawrence (Box A-52, Folder 149)
    - Hanlin, John (Box A-52, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: Louis Salzberg
    - Hanna, Bernard (Box A-52, Folder 151)
    - Hanna, Jacqueline (Box A-52, Folder 152)
    - Hanna, Roland (Box A-52, Folder 153)
    - Hannaham, Delora (Box A-52, Folder 154)
    - Hannaham, James H. (Box A-52, Folder 155)
    - Hannan, Philip M. (Box A-52, Folder 156)
    - Hannibal (Box A-52, Folder 157)
    - Hannibal, Ahmed (Box A-52, Folder 158)
    - Hannibal, Sonny (Box A-52, Folder 159)
    - Hannon, Barbara (Box A-52, Folder 160)
      Photographer if identified: Big M Photo Service
    - Hannon, Richard (Box A-52, Folder 161)
    - Hans, Jean (Box A-52, Folder 162)
    - Hansberry, Edward (Box A-52, Folder 163)
    - Hansberry, Lorraine (Box A-52, Folder 164)
    - Hansberry, Mamie (Box A-52, Folder 165)
    - Hansberry, William L. (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 166)
      Note on folder: "(See: Inactive File)."
    - Hansborough, Audrey Solomon (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 167)
      Folder label reads "Mrs. Audrey Solomon-Hansborough." Also one velox print.
    - Hansel + Gretel Club (Box A-52, Folder 168)
    - Hansen, Juliette (Box A-52, Folder 169)
    - Hanshaw, Chris (Chrysse) (Box A-52, Folder 170)
    - Hanshaw, Fred (Box A-52, Folder 171)
    - Hanson, Charles M. (Box A-52, Folder 172)
      Also one typescript leaf with envelope.
    - Hap Draper Duo (Box A-52, Folder 173)
    - Happy Ending (Box A-52, Folder 174)
      One print has paper stereotype matrix and ms. note attached with paperclip.
    - Harambee (Box A-52, Folder 175)
    - Harambee Prep 1971 (Box A-52, Folder 176)
    - Harari (Box A-52, Folder 177)
    - Hardaway, Mark (Box A-52, Folder 178)
    - Hardaway, Rose (Box A-52, Folder 179)
    - Hardeman, Buddy (Box A-52, Folder 180)
    - Harden, K. Albert (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 181)
    - Harder, Mel (Box A-52, Folder 182)
    - Harder, Pam (Box A-52, Folder 183)
      Photographer if identified: Doug Smart Associates
    - Hardge, Arthur (Rev.) (Box A-52, Folder 184)
    - Hardgrove, Ernest (Box A-52, Folder 185)
    - Hardiesty, Petronela (Pat) (Box A-52, Folder 186)
    - Hardin, Clifford M. (Box A-52, Folder 187)
      Photographer if identified: USDA Photo
    - Hardin, Helen (Box A-52, Folder 188)
    - Harding, Barbara (Box A-52, Folder 189)
    - Harding, Ellerine (Box A-52, Folder 190)
    - Harding, Eric A. (Box A-52, Folder 191)
    - Harding, Frederick L. (Box A-52, Folder 192)
    - Harding, Gina J. (Box A-52, Folder 193)
    - Harding, James H. (Box A-52, Folder 194)
      Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Curt Clemons, Allen Morgan
    - Harding, Jim (Box A-52, Folder 195)
    - Harding, Marilyn (Box A-52, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: M. Jaffe
    - Harding, Ray (Box A-52, Folder 197)
    - Harding, Thomas (Box A-52, Folder 198)
    - Harding, Vincent (Professor) (Box A-52, Folder 199)
    - Harding, Walter L. (Box A-52, Folder 200)
    - Hardins, Helen E. (Box A-52, Folder 201)
    - Hardison, Alex A. (Box A-52, Folder 202)
    - Hardison, Inge (Box A-52, Folder 203)
      Photographer if identified: Rufus Merritt, Bro. David McAdams
    - Hardmond, Robert (Rev.) (Box A-52, Folder 204)
      Photographer if identified: Leo Rosenthal, Bro. David McAdams
    - Hardwick, Arthur (Box A-52, Folder 205)
    - Hardwick, J.E. (Mr.) (Box A-52, Folder 206)
    - Hardy, Albert (Box A-52, Folder 207)
    - Candice, Hardy (Box A-52, Folder 208)
    - Hardy, E.L. (Rev.) (Box A-52, Folder 209)
    - Hardy, Gerald (Box A-52, Folder 210)
    - Hardy, Gladys (Box A-52, Folder 211)
      Photographer if identified: Ernest Agnew
    - Hardy, Jackie (Box A-52, Folder 212)
    - Hardy, Marie (Mrs.) (Box A-52, Folder 213)
    - Hardy, Michelle (Box A-52, Folder 214)
    - Hardy, Oliver (Box A-52, Folder 215)
    - Hardy, William Jr. (Box A-52, Folder 216)
    - Hare, Ethelene (Box A-52, Folder 217)
    - Hare, Nathan (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 218)
    - Harewood, Dorian (Box A-52, Folder 219)
    - Hargett, Ernest (Box A-52, Folder 220)
    - Hargett, James (Box A-52, Folder 221)
    - Hargrave, Rhonda (Box A-52, Folder 222)
    - Hargrave, Ruth M. (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 223)
    - Hargraves, J. Archie (Rev.) (Box A-52, Folder 224)
    - Hargrove, Andrew (Box A-52, Folder 225)
    - Harkless, James (Box A-52, Folder 226)
    - Harkness, Jerry (Box A-52, Folder 227)
    - Harlan, Diane (Box A-52, Folder 228)
    - Harleston, Bernard W. (Dr.) (Box A-52, Folder 229)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Lensman Photo, Bill Price
    - Harlem 5 (Box A-52, Folder 230)
    - Harlem 10K Race (Box A-52, Folder 231)
      Photographer if identified: Luigi, Lem Peterkin, A. Hansen Photography, Pictorial Enterprise, Lensman
    - Harlem Adult Training Center (Box A-52, Folder 232)
    - Harlem Athletic League (Box A-52, Folder 233)
    - Harlem Assertion of Rights Inc. (Box A-52, Folder 234)
      Photographer if identified: James Johnson Jr.
    - Harlem Blues & Jazz Band, The (Box A-52, Folder 235)
    - Harlem Boys Choir, The (Box A-52, Folder 236)
      Also one velox, one photocopied newspaper clipping, and one promotional flier.
      Photographer if identified: Johan Elbers, Pictorial Enterprise, Bryan D. Hall, Eugene Richards, Corporate Photographers
    - Harlem Business Alliance (Box A-52, Folder 237)
    - Harlem Children's Theatre Co. (Box A-52, Folder 238)
      Also five velox prints (stuck together) and one typescript leaf.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, David Thomas
    - Harlem Chorale (Box A-52, Folder 239)
    - Harlem Commonwealth (Box A-52, Folder 240)
    - Harlem Community Center Police Athletic League (Box A-52, Folder 241)
    - Harlem Consumer Frauds Bureau (Box A-52, Folder 242)
    - Harlem Co-op (Box A-52, Folder 243)
    - Harlem Cultural Council (Box A-52, Folder 244)
    - Harlem Dance Theatre (Box A-52, Folder 245)
    - Harlem Day (Box A-52, Folder 246)
    - Harlem-Dowling (Box A-52, Folder 247)
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Peter M. Lerman
    - Harlem Embers (Box A-52, Folder 248)
    - Harlem Girl Scouts (Box A-52, Folder 249)
    - Harlem Globetrotters (Box A-53, Folder 1)
    - Harlem Hall of fame (Box A-53, Folder 2)
      Photographer if identified: Dave
    - Harlem on the Hudson (Box A-53, Folder 3)
    - Harlem Inaugural (Box A-53, Folder 4)
      Also 6 velox prints (stuck together with paste).
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, A. Hansen
    - Harlem Independent Package stores (Box A-53, Folder 5)
    - Harlem Institute of Fashions (Box A-53, Folder 6)
      Also one typescript leaf and one velox print.
    - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service (Box A-53, Folder 7)
    - Harlem, Lawyers assoc. Dinner Com (Box A-53, Folder 8)
      Also one ms. leaf and one velox print.
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Wilson, Harris Photo
    - Harlem Liquor Salesman Boycott (Box A-53, Folder 9)
    - Harlem Mothers Assoc (Box A-53, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Neighborhood Assoc (Box A-53, Folder 11)
      One print has ms. text written on verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bill Anderson